{
    "subject": "Nasser_Taghvai",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Captain_Khorshid",
    "human_readable": "Nasser Taghvai directed Captain Khorshid.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8365685343742371,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Captain Khorshid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.787708580493927,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie directed by Nasser Taghvai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6587455868721008,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Nasser Taghvai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5793128609657288,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in Captain Khorshid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5302020311355591,
            "question": "What year was Captain Khorshid released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5126100182533264,
            "question": "Is Captain Khorshid a well-known movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4861268103122711,
            "question": "Where was Captain Khorshid filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4152393937110901,
            "question": "What genre is Captain Khorshid likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35098162293434143,
            "question": "What awards has Captain Khorshid won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3417586386203766,
            "question": "What themes does Captain Khorshid explore?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nasser Taghvai directed Captain Khorshid.",
            "html": "yago_10653_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What awards has Captain Khorshid won?",
            "html": "yago_10653_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Captain Khorshid likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_10653_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Captain Khorshid filmed?",
            "html": "yago_10653_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10653_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10653_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10653_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10653_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10653_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10653_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10653_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10653_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10653_97.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10653_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that \"Captain Khorshid\" is an Iranian film written and directed by Nasser Taghvai, and also provide details about the film's adaptation of Ernest Hemingway's novel, its awards, and the director's career. Therefore, the triple \"Nasser Taghvai directed Captain Khorshid.\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Nasser Taghvai directed Captain Khorshid.\" Several entries mention this film and attribute it to Nasser Taghvai as the director, such as in the document with file path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_10653/re-ranker-msmarco/77.txt`."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}